好了  准备好大玩一场了吗
Okay, who's ready to have some <i>fun?!</i>
你们是不是没听见啊  我说的是
I guess you didn't hear me. What I said was.
准备好大玩一场了吗
Who's ready to have some <i>fun?!</i>
老妈  别见怪  每当你说要大玩一场的时候
Mom, no offense, but whenever you say something's gonna be fun,
都不好玩
It's <i>not!</i>
这次不一样了
Until now,
因为这是首次  也是最后一次
Because it is time for the first and last
邓肯小宝宝的征名活动
Duncan family baby naming contest!
还是不好玩
And the streak continues.
听着  你们几个  获胜者的奖品就是
Okay, you guys, the prize is the satisfaction.
给你们的小弟弟或者小妹妹起名字的满足感
Of having named your baby brother or sister.
还有五块钱
And five bucks.
好了  别这样  你们几个  谁先来
Okay, come on, you guys. Who wants to get the ball rolling?
我先来  如果是女孩  叫“埃里卡”
I'll go. If it's a girl, "Erika."
如果是男孩  叫“诺亚”
If it's a boy, "Noah."
“埃里卡”和“诺亚”
"Erika" and "Noah."
有点意思  你怎么想到的
Those are very interesting. Where'd you get those?
灵光乍现
First things that popped into my head.
我来吧
I'll go.
女孩叫 “雪梨”  男孩叫“约拿”
If it's a girl, "Sydney." if it's a boy, "Jonah."
我可是费了很多心思在这两个名字上
Now I actually put some thought into these names.
我之所以选“约拿”是源于那部经典的
I chose "Jonah" after the character in the classic...
好了  下一个是谁
Okay, who's next?
我来吧  男孩叫“托比”
I'll go. If it's a boy, "Toby."
如果是女孩  无所谓了
If it's a girl, I don't care.
好吧  “托比”
Okay, "Toby."
那我把这里填上
And I'll just gonna fill in...
“詹妮”吧
"Jenny."
你呢  查莉  你想起个名字吗
How about you, Charlie? You wanna pick some names?
“糖糖”
Candy.
噢  挺可爱的  男孩叫什么
Oh, that's cute. For a boy?
热狗
Hot dog.
好吧  热狗·邓肯  获胜者出炉啦
Okay, Hot Dog Duncan. We have a winner!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第六集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E06  Name That Baby
-嘿  乖女儿  今天怎么样啊  -现在不是时候
-Hey, honey, how is your school? -Not now.
泰迪  你没事吧
Teddy, you okay?
我没时间回答这些问题
I don't have time for all these questions.
我明天有个欧洲史的期末考试
I have a huge european history final tomorrow.
-好吧  别慌  -别慌
-Okay, take it easy. -Easy?
这个占我一半的总评成绩
It's worth half of my grade.
另外这是高三下学期了
Plus it's second semester, junior year,
所以这对考大学至关重要
So these are the most important grades for college.
如果我考不上大学  就找不到好工作
If I don't get into college, I won't have a good career.
也嫁不到好人家  生活悲催了
Or a nice family or a happy life!
一着不慎  满盘皆输啊  同志们
Everything's on the line here, people.
哇
Wow.
希望咱们的小热狗不会有这么大的压力
I Hope hot dog doesn't get this stressed out.
嘿  老爸  嘿  老妈
Hey, dad. Hey, mom.
嘿  这不是毕业生吗
Hey, there are High School graduates.
他们说这是不可能的
And they said it couldn't be done.
别逗了  埃米特  谁说的
Come on, Emmett, who said that?
我爸  我妈
My dad, my mom,
很多老师
Most of my teachers.
好像还有你  邓肯叔
I think you did, Mr. Duncan.
别在意  他们都说错了
Well, they were all wrong.
不敢相信我的宝贝要毕业了
I can't believe my baby's gonna graduate.
不敢相信她的宝贝不能毕业了
I can't believe her baby's not gonna graduate.
等等  等等  等等  你说啥
Wait wait wait. What do you mean?
我发现我的体育没及格
I just found out I got an incomplete in p.E.
也就是说我拿不到毕业证了
That means I'm not gonna get my diploma.
等一下  我要毕业了  而你不成
Wait, I'm graduating and you're not?
正和幼儿园的时候相反
This is like the exact opposite of kindergarten.
我父母会崩溃的  真是场灾难
My parents are gonna be crushed, man. This is a disaster.
老兄  你不能放弃啊  和你的老师谈谈
Dude, you can't give up. Just talk to your teacher,
求求情  你们老师是谁
Work something out. Who is it?
石锤先生
Mr. Hammerstone.
狂人石锤吗
Madman hammerstone?
不是  是毛毛兔石锤
No, Fluffy bunny hammerstone.
那你应该没事
Then you should be fine.
好了  查莉  宝贝
Okay, Charlie, honey,
我们想和你谈一件很重要的事情
We have something very very important to talk to you about.
你知道我们将迎来一位新宝宝了  对吧
Now you know we have a new baby on the way, right?
在哪儿
Where is it?
在妈咪的肚肚里
It's in mommy's tummy.
-你把它吃了  -没有
-Did you eat it? -No.
爸爸吃的
Did daddy?
嘿  盖比在这儿呢
Hey, Gabe's here.
你想消失一下吗
You wanna not be here?
好了  查莉  当这位新宝宝出生后
Okay, Charlie, now when the new baby comes home,
爸爸和妈妈  将会花一些时间在他或她身上
Mommy and daddy, we're gonna have to spend a lot of time with him or her,
但这并不意味着我们对你的爱变少了
But that doesn't mean that we love you any less.
没错  当你们还都是小宝宝的时候
That's right. We love all of our babies the same.
我们都付出了同样多的爱
And every one of you has been a baby.
PJ还是宝宝的时候  泰迪还是宝宝的时候
P.J. Was a baby. Teddy was a baby.
盖比是宝宝的时候
Gabe was a baby.
先让我搞清楚了
So let me get this straight.
当爸爸跟我玩躲猫猫的时候  他不是真的消失了
When dad plays peek-a-boo with me, he doesn't actually disappear?
-没有  他只是藏在了手的后面  -确定吗
-No, he's just behind his hands. -Are you sure?
难道我们每天都要讨论这种问题吗
Do we have to have this conversation every day?
-我饿了  -我也是
-I'm hungry. -Me, too.
我也想吃了
I could eat.
-准备好了吗  -数到三
-Shall we? -On three.
等等  谁知道怎么数到三
Wait, does anyone know how to count to three?
三
Three.
她的小脑袋瓜里想什么呢
What can possibly be going through that little head of hers?
谁知道啊
I have no idea.
嗨  艾薇
Hi, Ivy.
不  说实话  我现在不能聊天
No, actually, I can't talk right now.
我要为了明天的欧洲史期末考试复习
I have to study for my european history final tomorrow,
除非你想谈谈克里米亚战争
So unless you wanna talk about the crimean war...
喂
Hello?
妈
Mom.
Mom!
妈  妈啊
Mom! Mom!
-妈  -盖比  你吼什么呢
-Mom! -Gabe, what are you doing?
看不出来吗  喊老妈呢
Isn't it obvious? I'm calling mom.
妈
Mom!
老弟  你上楼不成吗  我在学习呢
Dude, just go upstairs. I'm trying to study.
这事很重要  妈
It's important. Mom!
噢  我的铅笔找到了
Oh, here's my pencil.
盖比  你找我啊
<i>Gabe, did you need me?</i>
-没事了  -啥
-Never mind. -<i>What?</i>
-我说没事了  -好吧
-I said never mind! -<i>Okay.</i>
-你闹够了吗  -恩  够了
-Are you done? -Yeah, I'm done.
等一下  我的尺子呢
Wait, where's my ruler?
妈
Mom!
-啥  -呃
-<i>What?!</i> <i>-Ugh!</i>
妈  我在学习呢
Mom, I'm trying to study,
但盖比老嚷嚷
But Gabe keeps yelling.
宝贝  如果你需要个安静的环境  这里不是很好吗
Sweetie, if you need a quiet place to study, why don't you just do it here?
我在这练练瑜伽  我会带上耳机的
I'm just doing my yoga. I'll put on my headphones.
不会打扰到你的
Won't bother you at all.
-谢了  老妈  -恩
-Thanks, mom. -<i>Mm-hmm.</i>
您干啥呢
What are you doing?
练气息
The breath of fire.
好吧  您能把气息灭了吗
Well, could you extinguish it?
我刚练上
I just lit it.
我还是去厨房学吧
I'll study in the kitchen.
啥
What?
-嗨  老爸  -嘿  宝贝
-Hi, dad. -Hey, sweetie.
爸  你打算切多长时间
Dad, how long do you think that's gonna take?
欲速则不达
Do you want it fast or you want it yummy?
这么说来  老爸老妈跟你谈了
So mom and dad were giving you.
那个“新生儿动员会”  是吧
The old "new baby pep talk," huh?
算了  忘了吧  查莉
Well, forget it, Charlie.
一旦新宝宝降临  你就不是心头肉了
Once that new baby comes along, you're just another middle child.
欢迎来到被遗忘的孩子俱乐部
Welcome to the forgotten kids club.
希望你缅怀一下掌中宝的感觉
I Hope you enjoyed the spotlight,
因为已经结束了
'cause that's over.
没有  没结束
No, it's not.
否决  聪明
Denial. That's smart.
多用这招
Use that.
这才让我熬过幼儿园的
That's what got me through kindergarten.
-嘿  亲爱的  -老鲍  过来
-Hey, honey. -Bob, get over here.
我刚听到盖比和查莉的谈话
I just heard Gabe talking to Charlie.
他说一旦新生儿降临  我们就会把她遗忘的
He said we're gonna forget about her when the new baby comes along.
啥  我们怎能遗忘小可爱查莉呢
What? How could we forget about sweet little Charlie?
-她那么可爱  -我知道  但他呢
-She's adorable. -I know, but what about him?
-谁  -盖比
-Who? -Gabe!
他有种被忽视的感觉
He's feeling neglected.
也许我们没有花足够的时间来陪他
Maybe we're not spending enough time with him.
你胡说什么呢  我刚陪他打棒球去了
What are you talking about? I just took him to the batting cages.
那是他八岁那年
When he was 8.
好吧  那他现在多大了  十  十一
Okay, so, what is he now, 10, 11?
十三
13.
他还喜欢棒球吗
Is he still into baseball?
石锤先生
Mr. Hammerstone.
你想干嘛  小蛋糕
What do you want, cupcake?
-我是PJ  -你再说一遍
-It's P.J. -Excuse me?
叫我小蛋糕也成  我喜欢吃小蛋糕
Cupcake works. I like cupcake.
听着  我想找你谈谈我的成绩
Listen, I want to talk to you about my grade.
-你给我了个不及格  -恩
-You gave me an incomplete... -Mm-hmm.
也就是说我明天不能毕业
...Which means I can't graduate tomorrow.
看样子是个麻烦事
So kind of big problem.
对我来说不是
Not for me.
问题是  我只错过了一个项目
The thing is, though, I only missed one unit.
是最重要的项目
The most important unit of all...
可以让你升级为爷们的项目
The one that molds you into a man.
这个项目集竞技与纪律为一身
The one that combines athleticism and discipline,
为了你日后可以从容面对残酷的现实生活
And prepares you for the hard realities of life.
方块舞吗
Square dancing?
没错  小蛋糕
That's right, cupcake.
别见怪啊  但这好像不是那么重要吧
No offense, but it just doesn't seem that important.
“不重要”
"Not important."
如果当你走在街上
What if you're walking down the street.
然后  嘣  方块舞会迎面而来
And... bang! ... A hoedown breaks out?
打得你措手不及
You wouldn't be prepared.
好吧  你说的有理
Well, you do make a good point there.
听着  我真的希望准时毕业  有什么可以弥补的吗
Listen, I really wanna graduate on time. Isn't there anything I can do?
-这个  唯有一事  -什么事
-Well, there is one thing. -Yes.
明天之前学跳方块舞
You can learn how to square dance by tomorrow.
只有一个问题
Just one little problem...
就是无法完成
It's impossible.
噢  是吗  我觉着可以完成
Oh, yeah? I say it can be done.
我这就去学怎么跳方块舞
I'm gonna learn how to square dance by tomorrow.
那我准备不再管大家叫小蛋糕了
And I'm gonna stop calling everybody cupcake.
那是不可能滴  小蛋糕
Ain't gonna happen, cupcake!
-嘿  小泰  -嗨
-Hey, T. -Hi.
-你怎么来了  -我遇到难题了
-What are you doing here? -I didn't know what to do.
-我无处可去了  -怎么了  亲爱的
-I've got no place else to go. -What's wrong, honey?
今天够悲催的  我明天就要期末考试了
I've had the worst day. I have this big final tomorrow,
而我却找不到一个安静的地方学习
And I can't find a quiet place to study.
-我想在自己的屋里  可是  -是你妈吗
-I tried my house but... -Was it your mom?
大家都很吵
It was everybody.
但主要的还是你妈
But mainly your mom.
泰迪  这里永远欢迎你  来吧
Teddy, you are always welcome here. Come on.
坐下吧  千万别见外
Go on, you just get yourself comfortable,
我给你倒杯茶
And I will make you some tea.
呃  俺怎么从没受过这种待遇
Um, how come you never do any of this for me?
学习的人才有资格
I do this for people who study.
那还是算了
Not worth it.
嘿  他来了
Hey, there he is.
我们翘首以盼良久了
There's the guy we've been waiting for.
宝贝  我们看见这台卡拉OK机
Honey, we saw this karaoke machine,
就想到了你
And we thought of you.
因为
Because...?
因为我们可以一起唱歌啊
Because we can sing together.
因为
Because...?
因为这会很有趣的
Because it'll be <i>fun.</i>
这是要惩罚我吗
Am I being punished?
不是
No.
你妈和我发现我们最近很少陪你
Your mom and I thought we just hadn't had enough "gabe time" lately.
噢
Oh.
你们想说的不是因为在母亲节的时候
You're not talking about one of those stupid homemade coupons
我给你们的自制优惠券
I gave on mother's day, are you?
因为已经过期了
Because those expired.
不是啦  亲爱的  我们只是想多花点时间来陪陪你
No, honey, we just want to spend more time with you.
好了  你先看看这个
Okay, now you look at this.
然后选一首歌
And pick out any song you want.
你选的同时  我先吼两句
And while you're doing that, I'll do this.
老鲍  这不是合唱
Bob, it's not a duet.
是啊  从来就没有合唱  亲爱的
No, it never is, honey.
组成方形  再往后撤
<i>Form a square</i> <i>and back you go</i>
见见你的舞伴  换换你的舞步
<i>Now meet your honey</i> <i>with a do-si-do</i>
小鸡在热锅里  啄着生面团
<i>Chicken in the bread pan</i> <i>pecking at dough</i>
跳向我的卢  我的心头肉
<i>Skip to my Lou,</i> <i>my darlin'</i>
不对  不对  不对  对了
No no no no. Yep.
好的  继续  继续
Okay, go, keep going.
女士们  跳啊  男士们  你们都清楚
<i>Ladies, do</i> <i>and, gents, you know</i>
向你的舞伴鞠躬  然后开始跳  让她旋转
<i>It's bow to your partner</i> <i>and off you go, swing</i> <i>her around...</i>
-咱们休息下吧  -没时间了  我必须要学会
-Let's take a break. -We don't have time. I gotta learn this.
PJ  我们已经练了三个小时了
P.J., we've been at it for over three hours,
但你还是不会变换舞步
And you still don't know a "do-si" from a "do."
那你干嘛还一直喊“好啊  好啊”
Then why do you keep saying "good good"?
我是夸我自己呢  我跳得太好了
I was talking about me. I was killing it.
就这样了吗  不能毕业了吗
So that's it? I'm not gonna graduate?
-抱歉  老兄  -噢  天啊
-Sorry, buddy. -Oh man.
刚刚勉强过了“生什么学”和“几什么学”
After barely passing the subjects that end in "ology" and "ometry,"
没想到会栽倒在“舞什么学”上
I never thought it would be "ancing" that took me down.
给你看看当我们像你这么大的时候
We're wanna show you one of our favorite movies
一部爱看的电影
From when we were your age.
你绝对喜欢  关于一只大乌贼的
You're gonna love this. It's about a giant squid.
让整个海滩都陷入了恐惧之中
That terrorizes a small beach community.
叫做“触角来袭”
It's called "Tentacles Over Pismo."
我还常常做噩梦呢
I still have nightmares about it.
但你别怕  我们会全程陪伴你的
But don't worry, we will be right here with you the whole time.
你还要陪我多长时间啊
How much longer is "gabe time" gonna last?
宝贝  我们只想让你清楚
Sweetie, we just want you to know.
尽管你不是最小的孩子
That just because you're the middle kid.
并不意味着你是被遗忘的
Doesn't mean you're the forgotten kid.
噢
Oh!
你们偷听我说的
You guys overheard me say...
嘘  电影开始了
Shh! Movie's starting.
来吧  钻到妈妈的怀里
Come on now, snuggle with mommy.
呦  什么东西
<i>Eww! What's that?</i>
是只触角
<i>It's an arm.</i>
是八只触角
It's eight arms.
够吓人的  是吧
Pretty scary, huh?
得了吧  乌贼还戴着手表呢
Come on, the squid's wearing a watch.
凯瑟琳大帝
Catherine the great.
凌晨一点
1:00 A.M.
还有七个小时就要考试了
Only seven more hours until this test.
振作啊  泰迪  集中注意力
Come on, Teddy, focus.
抱歉  温兹夫人  我吵醒你了吗
I'm sorry, Mrs. Wentz, did I wake you?
温兹夫人
Mrs. Wentz?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
-噢  又来了  -什么情况
-Oh no. -What's going on?
她又梦弹了
She's sleep-playing.
她什么
She's what?
有的人梦游  有的人说梦话
You know how some people sleepwalk and sleep-talk?
俺老娘梦中弹风琴
My mom plays the organ in her sleep.
你能叫醒她吗  我要学习了
Can you wake her up? I have to study.
你不能叫醒一个梦游者  很危险的
You can't wake up a sleepwalker. It's dangerous.
她快好了  只要她不开始唱歌  我们就没事
She'll be done soon. As long as she doesn't start singing, we're good.
噢  美丽的
O beautiful
广阔天空
For spacious skies
金色的
For Amber waves
麦田
Of grain...
她在致敬美国
It's her salute to America.
一时半会停不了
This'll take a while.
不敢相信
Unbelievable.
-你去哪  -车里
-Where you going? -My car, I guess.
找个安静的地方学习
Gotta find a quiet place to study.
完了吗
Is it over?
我的祖国啊
My country, 'tis of thee
可爱的自由之邦
Sweet land of liberty
我为您歌唱
Of thee I sing.
查理二世
<i>Charles II.</i>
你们在干吗
What are you doing?
你们不能拖走我的车
You can't tow my car!
我有个期末考试
I have a final!
查莉  我想和你谈点事情
<i>Charlie, I wanna talk</i> <i>to you about something.</i>
-关于我昨天所说的  -老鲍  老鲍  过来
-<i>About what</i> <i>I said yesterday... </i> <i>-Bob, Bob, get over...</i>
我说错了  你不用担心老爸老妈会遗忘你
<i>...I was wrong. You don't</i> <i>have to worry about mom</i> <i>and dad forgetting you.</i>
他们可能会很忙
<i>They might be busy,</i>
但他们对我们的爱  很深很深
<i>But they love us</i> <i>very much.</i>
-说得真好  -什么
-That is so sweet. -What is?
过来
Come on.
看来  盖比喜欢做一名被遗忘的孩子
Well, I guess Gabe enjoys being the forgotten kid.
是啊  看起来是这样的
Yeah, sure sounds like it.
嘿  知道吗  如果我们遗忘他
Hey, you know, if we were to forget him,
时不时的
Just every now and then...
也是一种不错的教育方式
That would be good parenting.
不如这样  我来完成我的任务
You know what? I think I'm going to do my part.
这周将他遗忘
And forget him this week.
我再无视他整个周末
And I shall ignore him all weekend.
恩  感觉不错
Mmm. Feels good.
是啊  做正确的事情  感觉总是那么好
Yeah, it always feels good to do the right thing.
看看啊  邓肯
Well, Duncan,
你在二十四小时之内搞定方块舞了吗
Did you master the art of square dancing in 24 hours?
说实话  没有
Actually, no.
那你戴着学士帽  穿着学士服干嘛
Then what are you wearing the cap and gown for?
听着  我父母在外面呢
Look, my parents are out there.
他们真心想看到我毕业
They <i>really</i> wanna see me graduate.
所以我来这里求你可怜可怜我  发发善心
So I came back here to appeal to your sense of mercy.
发发慈悲
And humanity and...
你有这些东西吗
Do you actually have any of those?
自从我带上口哨之后就没有了
Not since I started wearing the whistle.
我隆重欢迎本届的南方高中毕业班
I'd like to welcome this year's <i>south high graduating class!
咱们秋天再见  邓肯
<i>I'll see you in the fall,</i> <i>Duncan.</i>
嘿
Hey.
老爸  你怎么来了
Dad, what are you doing in here?
埃米特把所有事情都告诉我了
Emmett just told me everything that's going on,
所以我来帮你毕业来了
So I'm here to help you graduate.
算了  结束了  我做不到的
Forget it. It's over. I can't do it.
噢  你可以的  因为你姓邓肯
Oh yes, you can. You're a Duncan.
在你的血液里流淌着方块舞的天赋
You've got square dancing in your blood.
在高中的时候  我可是方块舞舞王
In High School, I was a square dancing champion.
哇  等一下
Whoa, wait a minute.
你是“迷踪步邓肯”吗
Are you "do-si-do Duncan"?
不提了  不提了  不提了  不提了
Whatever, whatever, whatever, whatever.
你是很厉害  老爸  但如何帮我呢
That's great for you, dad, but how does that help me?
可以这样帮你
It helps you like this.
好了  把手抬起来  好了吗
Okay, start with your hand up, all right?
嘿  跟着我的步伐
Hey, just follow my lead.
女士们跳舞  绅士们  都清楚
<i>ladies, do,</i> <i>and, gents, you know</i>
向你的舞伴鞠一躬  开始跳
<i>it's bow to your partner</i> <i>and off we go</i>
让她旋转  绅士们  你们知道的
<i>swing her around</i> <i>and, gents, you know</i>
一圈半之后  继续跳
<i>once and a half</i> <i>and off we go</i>
用你的左手  让她旋转
<i>swing your partner</i> <i>with your left hand</i>
顺势而为  左右转圈
<i>then follow that up</i> <i>with a right-left grand</i>
玉米在猪圈  豆子在麻袋
<i>corn in the pigpen,</i> <i>beans in the sack</i>
转完圈后  漫步走
<i>circle right</i> <i>then promenade back</i>
双手举起  绕着你走
<i>two hands up</i> <i>and around you go</i>
组成星形  变换舞步
<i>form a star,</i> <i>now do-si-do</i>
约上你的舞伴来跳阿勒曼德舞
<i>give your honey</i> <i>an allemande</i>
寻牡蛎  挖蛤蜊
<i>dive for the oyster,</i> <i>dig for the clam</i>
组成方形  继续跳
<i>form a square</i> <i>and back you go</i>
见见舞伴  换换舞步
<i>now meet your honey</i> <i>with a do-si-do</i>
小鸡在热锅里  啄着生面团
<i>chicken in the bread pan,</i> <i>pecking at dough</i>
跳向我的卢  我的心头肉
<i>skip to my Lou,</i> <i>my darlin'.</i>
真讨厌
Dang!
太美了
That was beautiful.
-意味着  -你可以毕业了  小蛋糕
-Does that mean... -You can graduate, cupcake.
呜  好了  我们走
Whoo! Come on, let's go.
好的  走吧
All right, let's go.
先生
Sir,
看见您跳方块舞真是我莫大的荣幸
It was an honor to watch you work the square.
好了  我会回来的
Well, I'll be back.
我还有个不会跳舞的闺女
I got a daughter who can't dance, either.
好消息啊  查莉
Great news, Charlie.
猜猜是谁在欧洲史的期末考试上拿到了个优
Guess who got an "A" on her european history final.
结果发现学习圣地
Turns out the perfect place to study.
是在早上六点的拖车办公室
Is at a tow truck office at 6:00 in the morning.
我真的很为你自豪
Well, I am very proud of you.
-说到自豪  -我毕业了
-And speaking of proud... -I graduated!
拿倒了  宝贝
It's upside down, honey.
还是毕业
I still graduated.
还有个消息
In other news,
每个人给新生儿取的名字
Everyone in the family has picked out two names for the new baby.
老爸老妈要在其中挑一个
Mom and dad are gonna choose from one of these.
有中意的吗  老妈
So any favorites, mom?
我可没说
I'm not saying.
我觉着“糖糖”和“热狗”会进入复赛的
I see that "candy" and "hot dog" have made a reappearance.
如果你和你的小弟弟一起在看这段录像
If you're watching this with your little brother hot dog,
祝他好运吧  查莉
Wish him lots of good luck, Charlie.
嘿  大伙
Hey, guys,
老爸老妈在商量宝宝自主上厕所的事情呢
Mom and dad were talking about this thing called potty training.
什么东西
What's that?
你知道走廊尽头的那个房间吗
You know that room at the end of the hall?
有把奇怪的椅子那间吗
The one with the weird chair?
是啊  那把椅子叫做马桶
Yeah, that chair is called a toilet.
他们要教我们如何使用
They're gonna make us learn how to use it.
马桶吗
Toilet?
为什么要换别的方式方便呢
What's wrong with the current system?
我就很喜欢尿布
I am very happy in diapers.
我也是  我也喜欢尿布
Me too. I love diapers.
但我不喜欢现在这个
Not loving this one, though.
是啊  我想换个新的
Yeah. I could go for a change.
准备好了吗
Shall we?
我来了
I'm coming.
厕所就不会有这种服务
<b>You don't get that kind of service on the toilet.</b>